(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T12:36:01.845327",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
答えは いつも 私の胸に
The answer is always in my heart...
なんでだろう
Why is it
あなたを選んだ私です
that I chose you?
もっと止まらない 運命様から 決められたけど
Unstoppable, decided by Lady Fate itself,
i believe 似たもの同士じゃ つまらないのよ you'll be right !
I believe just being birds of a feather is no fun! You'll be right!
感じるまま 感じる ことだけをするよ
I'll only do what I feel, exactly as I feel it.
冒険でしょでしょ！？
It's an adventure, right?
ホントが嘘に 変わる世界で
In a world where truth turns into lies,
夢があるから 強くなるのよ
I'll grow stronger because I have a dream.
誰のためじゃない
Not for anyone else's sake—
一緒に来てくだサイ
please come along with me!
どこまでも自由な 私を見ていてね
Watch me as I roam freely anywhere!
明日過去になった 今日の今が奇跡
Today, which becomes tomorrow's past, is a miracle.
i believe you...
戻れないところまで 行かなきゃつまらない
If I don't go past the point of no return, it's no fun.
さあ教えて 秘めてる願いを 鏡に投げた
Now tell me, I cast my hidden wish into the mirror.
my delight 体ごと受け止めれたら your mind fly !
My delight, if you embrace it with your all, your mind will fly!
驚かせて 驚いて 笑顔になろう
Let's surprise, be surprised, and smile!
始まりでしょでしょ！？ 綺麗が闇を 照らすみたいに
It's the beginning, right? Like beauty illuminating the dark.
私の力 あなたの涙 どっちも正しいの
My power, your tears—both of them are right.
答えはいつも私の胸に…
The answer is always in my heart...
なんだろ お前を選んだ私です
Why is it that I chose you?
もう止まらない 運命様から決められたけど
I've been picked by the unstoppable Lady Fate,
I believe
真似だけじゃつまらないのよ
that just imitating is boring.
You'll be right!
You'll be all right!
感じるまま感じることだけをするよ
I'll only feel the things that I'm feeling.
冒険でしょでしょ!?
It's an adventure, right, right!?
ホントが嘘に変わる世界で
In a world where truth changes into lies,
夢があるから強くなるのよ
I'm going to get stronger because I have a dream,
誰のためじゃない 一緒に来てください
Not for the sake of somebody. Please come with me!
どこまでも自由な私を見せてね
Look at me—I'm free everywhere I go!
明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
The present today that became the past tomorrow is a miracle.
I believe you...
戻れないところまで行かなくちゃつまらない
It's no fun if I don't go until I reach the point of no return.
さぁ教えて 秘めてる願いを鏡に投げた
Now, tell me! I cast off my hidden wishes into a mirror.
My delight
身体ごと受け入れたら
If I react to my delight with my whole body,
Your mind fly!
Your mind will fly!
驚かせて 驚いて 笑顔になろう
Let's surprise and be surprised, and smile.
始まりでしょでしょ!?
It's the beginning, right, right!?
綺麗が闇を照らすみたいに
Like how beauty illuminates the dark,
私のちから あなたの涙
My power, your tears,
どっちも正しいの
both of them are right.
現実に揺れる繊細な心が
A delicate heart that trembles in reality
傷つくのはいや
I don't want it to be hurt.
想いまして いつもいつも胸の奥に
I thought that the answer is always, always in my heart...
答えが…
...
普通じゃないのが当然なら
If it's natural to not be normal,
答える私は何ができる？
What can I do to answer?
普通でも普通じゃなくて
It's normal and yet it's not.
感じるまま感じることだけをするよ
I'll only feel the things that I'm feeling.
冒険でしょでしょ!?
It's an adventure, right, right!?
ホントが嘘に変わる世界で
In a world where truth changes into lies,
夢があるから強くなるのよ
I'm going to get stronger because I have a dream,
誰のためじゃない
Not for the sake of somebody.
始まりでしょ 始まりなんだろ!?
It's the beginning, right? It's the beginning, right!?
綺麗が闇を照らすみたいに
Like how beauty illuminates the dark,
私とあなた 冒険の途中
You and I are on the middle of an adventure.
一緒に進んでく どこまでも自由に
Let's advance together freely, through thick and thin
現実を超えて
And go beyond reality.
明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
The present today that became the past tomorrow is a miracle.
確かな未来を
A definite future
掴もう未来を
Let's take hold of the future.
I believe you...
あぁ、さっきのはすごくよかったね！
I think that was our best one yet!
そうだね！すごい同調したね！
Yeah! We synced better this time!
やっとできるようになると…体がバラバラになりそうくらい疲れたよ～
Took awhile to get it down though... My body feels like it's going to fall apart
疲れるにはまだ早いよ！まだ3回目のリバーサルだよ？
Don't fall over now! This is only what, our 3rd time practicing?
わかるけどさ～でも足に力が入ってないから買い直すためのソーイングキットちょうだい～
I know it is~ But I think I need the sewing kit on me, my legs feel loose
そもそもどうやってゾンビになったか教えて？
So... how did you get reincarnated anyways?
んーそうだね…
... That's actually a good question
私も思いついたことがなくて…気づいたらお墓から目が覚めて…
I never really thought about it I just suddenly rose from the dead and...
そのまま…
Went on with whatever...
え？今までなぜなかったか、どうやってなったかがわからないってこと？
So you're telling me that you don't even know how? Or why, even?
うん…なるほどね…
To be honest, yeah... I see...
それなら今やれば？今日も結構時間の余裕がだし、自分のことについて調べてみればどうかな？
Well, you have right now. So why don't you try to look into it just a bit?
え？でも今リバーサル中でしょ…
Huh? But we're in the middle of dance practice...
リバーサルは別の日に変更できるから気にしないで～
We can just practice another day! Don't worry too much~
ベスティー…大好き！
Bestie... I love you so so so much!
今度何か奢ってね！もちろん！
I promise I'll treat you! Haha! You better!
ではいってらっしゃい！戻ってきたら色々話してね！
Now get out of here! You better bring me a good story out of it!
えぇ！もちろん！
Heheh! I will!
あのね、私実は分かっているの
Hey, I'm actually coming to realize,
ほら、君が言ったこと
you know, that thing you said...
あまり考えたいと思えなくて忘れてたんだけど
It didn't seem like I really wanted to think about it much
盲目的に盲動的に妄想的に生きて
Living blindly, recklessly, full of delusions
衝動的な焦燥的な消極的なままじゃだめだったんだ
Impulsively, impatiently, half-heartedly; it was really no good.
きっと、人生最後の日を前に思うのだろう
I'm sure that before the final day of my life
全部、全部言い足りなくて惜しいけど
I'll think that it's regrettable I didn't get to say everything.
あぁ、いつか人生最後の日、君がいないことを
Ahh, someday on the last day of my life, you're not here
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、ちゃんと言って
Tell me more, more, more, more, properly, that you're not here.
あのね、空が青いのはってどうやって伝えればいいんだろうね
Hey, how should I convey to you the blueness of the sky, I wonder?
夜の雲が高いのはってどうすれば君もわかるんだろう
What should I do so you can also get just how high the clouds at night are?
言って。
Say it.
あのね、私実は分かっているの
Hey, I'm actually coming to realize, you know...
言って。
Say it.
あのね、私実は分かってるの ほら、君が言ったこと
Hey, I'm actually coming to realize, you know, that thing you said...
全部全部言い足りなくて惜しいけど、
Even though I wish I had said everything,
あぁ、いつか人生最後の日 君がいないことを
Ah, someday on the last day of my life, that you're not here...
もっと もっと もっと もっと
more, more, more, more...
もっと、ちゃんと言って
more, properly, say it.
あのね、空が青いのかってどうやって伝えればいいんだろうね
Hey, how should I convey to you the blueness of the sky, I wonder?
夜の雲が高いのかってどうすれば君もわかるんだろう
What should I do so you can also get just how high the clouds at night are?
言って
Say it.
あのね、私実は分かってるの もう君が逝ったこと
Hey, I actually already know that you've already passed on.
あのね、分からないって言うんだろうね 忘れたいんだけど
You'll probably call me a stubborn blockhead, right? I wanna forget, but...
もっとちゃんと言ってよ 忘れられないよ、デモにしてよ
Tell me properly so I won't forget, turn it into a demo.
明日十時にホームで待ち合わせとかしようぜ
Let's meet at the platform at 10 tomorrow, or something like that.
牡丹は散っても花だし 夏が去っても追慕は切だ
Even if the peony petals scatter, it's still a flower...
口に出して、声に出して
Put it into words, say it out loud,
君が言って
you say it.
そして人生最後の日 君が見えるのなら
And on the last day of my life, if I am able to see you,
きっと人生最後の日も愛を歌うのだろう
surely I'll be singing my love on the last day of my life as well.
全部全部無駄じゃなかったって言うから
I'll say none of it, none of it ended up being for nothing, so...
あぁ、いつか人生最後の日 君がいないことがまだ信じられないけど
Ah, someday on the last day of my life, I still won't be able to believe that you're gone, but...
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと
More, more, more, more,
もっと、もっと、ちゃんと言って
more, more, properly, say it.
昔は手伝ってくれた ステージの掃除を Ollie!
Thanks for helping us set up the stage, Ollie!
いやぁ、さっきケーブルがぐちゃぐちゃ全部、幸い先輩が手伝い直して本当に助かった！
Yeah! We kinda had troubles with the cables, good thing you helped us untangle them!
えへへ、問題ないよ！
Hehe! No problem!
もし私をせんのうは～？ここであなたたちに会えて嬉しい！
If anything, I'm really happy I got to catch you guys here!
私、少し相談があるの。
I actually have something in my head recently...
おっ、なになに？
Oh? What's up?
最近さ、私、ふと気になってるの。なぜゾンビになったんだろう…なんのために生まれたんだろうってね。
Lately I've been wondering... what the reason of my zombie becoming was...
こう、みんなにとって私はゾンビになった理由は何だと思う？
Why do you guys think I turned into a zombie?
おお、自分探しって時期か！
Oh, you're searching for your identity!
うん、もし私に言うなら、あなたが追い求めていることや希望がたくさんあって
Well, I think there are a lot hopes and things that you want to pursue...
その思いの強さがあなたを生きてさせてゾンビになったと思う。
Because of your strong will and hope, you got reanimated and turned into a zombie.
おお！そうかも！
That sounds close!
Zeta, あなたはどう思う？
What do you think is the reason, Zeta?
私の考えだと、先輩の体もっとたくさんの思い出を作りたいから。だから生き残ったのかもしれないですね！
Hmm I think your body just wants to make more happy memories! Maybe!
おお、面白い！みんなの意見をくれてありがとね！
I see, thanks so much for the input guys!
もしかしたらそれがピッタリの答えかも！
I think those are pretty spot on reasons!
どういたしまして！早く答えを見つけるといいね！
No problem! Hope you get to find your reason soon!
先輩頑張って！
Good luck senpai!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ？ 艶やかなこの唇
I know you want it, don't you? These glossy lips of mine
ヤワな男たち 惹きつける 息を呑む ほどに甘い密
Luring in all those fragile men, honey so sweet it takes your breath away
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know you want it,
艶やかな この唇
these glossy lips of mine,
ワヤな 男たち 惹き寄せる
attracting reckless men.
息を 噛む ほど に 甘い 蜜
Sweet nectar enough to bite my breath,
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know you want it,
二度見 する この 躰
this body you double-take at.
汗ばむ 街 一人 歩け ば
Walking alone through the sweat-soaked town,
淫ら な 視線 が 絡みつく
lewd gazes entwine around me.
ねえ 何 を 期待 し て いる の ?
Hey, what are you expecting?
そのうち じゃなくて 今 すぐ が いい の
Not eventually, I want it right now.
大人 の 恋 に 焦がれ て
Yearning for a mature love,
見た目 より も 残る あどけない
leaving behind more than just looks,
心 だけ が 先走る
only my heart races ahead.
青い 蕾 の まま 大人 振る舞う
Acting mature while still a blue bud,
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know you want it,
刺激 する 私 の 全て
provoking everything of mine.
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know you want it,
艶やかな この唇
these glossy lips of mine,
刺激 する 私 の 全て
provoking everything of mine,
冷め た 瞳 まで 魅了 する
mesmerizing even cold eyes.
いつか は 花 に なる アマリリス
Amaryllis that will someday become a flower.
優しい だけ の 言葉 じゃなくて
Not just gentle words,
心 で 繋がり たくて
wanting to connect by heart.
ありきたりな メイク じゃ 隠せない
Unhiding with cliché makeup,
憧れ だけ 夢 を 見る
dreaming only of yearning.
あなた の 前 では また 大人 振る舞う
Acting mature again in front of you.
追いかけて 追いかけて
Chasing, chasing,
また オトナブルー
once more otonablue.
優しい だけ の 言葉 じゃなくて
Not just gentle words,
心 で 繋がり たくて
wanting to connect by heart.
ありきたりな メイク じゃ 隠せない
Unhiding with cliché makeup,
憧れ だけ 夢 を 見る
dreaming only of yearning.
あなた の 前 では また 大人 振る舞う
Acting mature again in front of you.
優しい だけ の 言葉 じゃなくて
Not just gentle words,
心 で 繋がり たくて
wanting to connect by heart.
ありきたりな メイク じゃ 隠せない
Unhiding with cliché makeup,
憧れ だけ 夢 を 見る
dreaming only of yearning.
あなた の 前 では また 大人 振る舞う
Acting mature again in front of you.
追いかけて 追いかけて
Chasing, chasing,
また オトナブルー
once more otonablue.
Guh! Huph! Grrr...! yabei... meccha tsukareta!
Guuh! Huph! Grrr...! Man, I'm so exhausted!
Nooo! kawaiiii!
Nooo! So cute!
yappaa... mata makechatta!
Aw man... I lost again!
waa... sukiru no mondai ne...
Wow, talk about skill issue...
kore waa... bukan sukiru no mondai janai! kairanya aje yang terlalu op...
This is not about skill issue... It's just that Kaela is too OP...
senpai kalau latihan dikit juga jago kok, pasti!
Hehe, you'll get the hang of it, senpai~ Practice a little and you'll be great for sure!
Oh iya... bukannya kamu tadi nyariin kita karena katanya pengen nanyain sesuatu? Eh?
Oh yeah, didn't you have something you wanted to talk to us about? Oh?
iya ya! saking serunya main, aku sampe lupa!
Right! I got so reeled into the game that I forgot!
aku nyari kalian soalnya ada yang pengen aku konsulin. jadi... penanya kalian...
There's something that I'm curious about and I wanted to ask you guys...
wuih, konsul apa tuh? konsul restoran? aku tau banyak loh yang enak!
Are you taking us to dinner? I know the place! I know lots of good spots!
heh? bukan! aku tuh...
Nooo... That's not it! I...
lagi krisis identitas... atau lebih tepatnya lagi... krisis eksistensial. aku lagi heran gitu loh... kok bisa ya aku hidup kembali sebagai zombie?
I'm kind of in the middle of an existential crisis, literally... Trying to figure out why I was resurrected as a zombie in the first place...
dipikir-pikir... iya juga ya, kita nggak tau kenapa.
Come to think about it... Yeah, we never really knew why...
iya... kira-kira... kalian ada ide nggak kenapa?
Yeah... So any guesses? Do you guys have any idea why?
hmm, sebenarnya kalau menurut aku, senpai bosen aja kali ya ditiduran mulu di kuburan gitu jadi pengen bangun. ya gak sih, bingung juga.
Maybe your body is just bored of being buried? I don't know though, just tired of lying around in a grave, so you wanted to wake up? Who knows.
nah, nah, aku kira wong iki duwe dendam eh, dadi dewehe durung tenang afterlifenya.
I think she holds a grudge, so she can't find peace in her afterlife...
yoh... hmm, bisa juga... aku nggak pernah kepikiran sampe sana sih.
Huh, never really saw it that way. True, never really thought about it that way...
kalau Moona senpai bagaimana?
What about you, Moona-senpai, what do you think?
aku? hmm... mungkin sebelum mati kamu minum sesuatu? atau mungkin digigit sesuatu?
Me? Hmm... Maybe you drank something that prevented you from death? Or maybe got bitten by a mysterious creature?
yah, tapi alasan apapun itu... kamu tetap Ollie kita kok, Li!
Well... whatever the reason may be... you're still our Ollie, so I hope you know that...
kecuali... kalau ternyata senpai itu sebenarnya...
Unless you turn out to be... what she means to say is that...
maksudnya Kobo itu... senpai tuh mau bentuknya kayak bagaimanapun juga tetap teman kita.
You'll still be our friend, senpai, no matter what form you take...
aww thanks guys! ya udah... aku mau tanya-tanya orang lagi ya!
Aww thanks guys! Well... I'm going to ask around a bit more!
semangat latihannya! oke dadah senpai! dadah... semoga ketemu ya lore-nya!
Good luck with practice! See you! Good luck with your lore finding!
朝まで踊る夢だけ見せて
Show me only the dream of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が解く魔法
The magic unlocked by the clock's bell
曖昧な指誘う階段三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
Vague fingers beckon down the stairs, bounding three steps at a time
馬車の中で震えていたみすぼらしい古着
Trembling inside the carriage in shabby old clothes
めぐり巡れ夜の舞踏
Turn around the night dance
見知らぬ顔探す囁くあの声が
Searching for unfamiliar faces, that whispering voice
握り締めた刃突き立てすべてを奪えと
Thrusts a clenched blade demanding to take everything
孤児集める城笑い仮面に描いて
The castle gathering orphans, painted on a smiling mask
偽りの慈しみさえ羽で包む熾天使
Even false mercy, a seraph wrapped in feathers
灰中で赤く溶け混じる硝子の靴今更帰る震えているの
Glass shoes melting red in the ashes, trembling as I return now
あなたが目を見やる時刻靴脱ぎ踊るスロープ抜けて
The time when you look into my eyes, dancing past the slope
喉まで伸びる指の先で
With fingertips reaching up to my throat
すくう雫口づけ走る衝動
Scooping drops, kissing, the impulse to run
背骨抜けていく刹那鐘は鳴らさないで
The moment my spine goes numb, don't ring the bell
あなたにひざまずきまだダメと叫んだ右手
Kneeling before you, my right hand screaming 'not yet'
が突き刺すサヨナラ消せない硝煙を香水に纏う姫
Thrusts into a farewell, a princess draped in smoke as perfume
強い瞳僕の凍った仮面ごと突き抜く
Strong eyes pierce right through my frozen mask
今も耳にあなたの吐息が
Your breath still pierces my ears
突き刺すの遠い夢ステンドグラス越し光る月が
In a distant dream, the moon shining through stained glass
君にかぶせたベールドレス膝で裂けて
The veil placed over you, my dress torn at the knees
ティアラは投げ捨てて見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Throwing the tiara aside, eyes gazing into each other
火花を放つ孤独な魂が炎上げ惹かれあう
Emit sparks, lonely souls raise flames and are drawn to each other
その涙すくいえないならまるで一人遊び
If you cannot wipe away those tears, it's like playing alone
時よ止まれ今はあなたに酔いしれて
Stop time now, intoxicated by you
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを刻み付けていたい
I want to carve every single swaying heartbeat
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay, hot and wet
打ち付ける昂ぶりに
To the pounding excitement
朝まで踊る夢だけ見せて時計の鐘が解く魔法
Show me only the dream of dancing until morning, the magic unlocked by the clock's bell
ステンドグラス越し光る月が君にかぶせたベール
The moon shining through stained glass, the veil placed over you
ドレス膝で裂けてティアラは投げ捨てて
My dress torn at the knees, throwing the tiara aside
見つめあう瞳と瞳が火花を放つ
Eyes gazing into each other emit sparks
孤独な魂が炎上げ惹かれあう
Lonely souls raise flames and are drawn to each other
その涙すくいえないならまるで一人遊び
If you cannot wipe away those tears, it's like playing alone
時よ止まれ今はあなたに酔いしれて
Stop time now, intoxicated by you
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを刻み付けていたい
I want to carve every single swaying heartbeat
とどまれ熱く濡れ打ち付ける昂ぶりに
Stay, hot and wet, to the pounding excitement
これ以上は動けないよ
I cannot move any more than this
まるで千夜より
Like more than a thousand nights
深く沈む砂のようにまどろむ
Slumbering like sand sinking deep
今も耳にあなたの吐息が突き刺すの遠い夢
Your breath still pierces my ears in a distant dream
ステンドグラス越し光る月が君にかぶせたベール
The moon shining through stained glass, the veil placed over you
ドレス膝で裂けてティアラは投げ捨てて
My dress torn at the knees, throwing the tiara aside
見つめあう瞳と瞳が火花を放つ
Eyes gazing into each other emit sparks
孤独な魂が炎上げ惹かれあう
Lonely souls raise flames and are drawn to each other
...zzzzz... zzzzzz...
Hmm..? Huh..?
な、おめ…？
Wh- What...-?
宮び先輩？！
Miyabi-senpai?!
あ、目が覚めたんだね。おはよう
Ah, you're awake. Good morning.
み、宮び先輩？！ここで何してるの？
M-Miyabi-senpai?! What are you doing here?
今日は僕もスタジオでのダンスリハーサルがあるんだ。
I have dance practice in the studio today too...
歩いてたら道端で寝ているオリーを見つけてさ。
And then I found you sleeping here in the wayside...
オリーはなんでここで寝ていたの？
And what about you? Why were you sleeping here?
お、う…あ…
Oh... Uh... Uh...
ちょっと長くなるけど
It's kind of a long story...
最近 自分の存在の理由が気になって
Lately, I've been thinking about my origins...
あ
Ah.
オリーの実家がラーメン屋に変わったから起きたんじゃないの？
Isn't it because your house turned into a ramen shop? Or so I heard.
違うよ！
That's wrong!
それはたまたま起きた時にラーメン屋だった
I happen to wake up and it already was a ramen shop...
それでね
And you know?
自分の存在について考え始めて
The more I think about my existence...
自分の運命まで考えちゃって
The more I think about fate...
なぜ運命がオリーを起こしたんだろう
Why did it make me live, I wonder?
死んだ後に未練でもあるのかな
Why is my grave not the end of my chapter? Can't help it...
そういうことがあったんだ
I see, so you've been having those thoughts...
大変だね
It must be hard for you to think about.
でも、たまに考えずにそのままにしといたほうがいいこともあるのって知ってる？
But you know, sometimes there are things that are best left as is...
だから、深く考えないでそのうち答えが出てくるからさ
I don't think you need to ponder too much about it, surely the answer will come to you on its own...
そうだね、その通りだね
You know what... you're right, senpai...
焦る必要もないし、いつかきっと答えが出てくるはず！
I shouldn't rush too much... Surely I'll find out sooner or later!
役に立ってよかった
I'm glad I got to help you...
じゃあ、リハがあるから先にいってくるね
Anyways, I have dance practice so I better take my leave now.
うん！先輩、本当にありがとう！
I will! Thank you so much, senpai!
元気でね、オリー
Take care, Ollie!
先輩、その通りだ…考えすぎなくていい
He's right... I shouldn't think about it too much...
必ず答えが出てくる
I should just take my time...
あ、結局…私、何で答えばっかり探し回ってんだろ
In the end, I just wasted my day looking for an answer that I don't even exist...
イオフィ先輩とのリハーサルまでサボっちゃって…後で謝らなくちゃ…
I feel bad for bailing on dance practice with lofi-senpai... I gotta apologize later...
「答えが必ず出てくるってね…」
"The answer will come to me sooner or later," huh...
いや、もがもが答えががあれば…再び死ぬ前に答えが出るといいな…
I hope I won't have to wait too long that I get revived a second time...
あんまり手がかりがあるといいのに…
If only there was some sort of clue...
これは…お花？こんなところに、道端に生えているかな？不思議
Is that a flower? What's it doing growing at a busy street like this? How weird.
これって、ここ生えてくるんじゃないの？小さいお花。ほら、ここで咲くべき…
This isn't your place, little daisy. You belong somewhere else...
ここで生えたら枯れちゃうよ
If you were to stay, then you'll only wilt...
ばるさん？な、何が起きたの？
W-What... Just... Happened...?
花が…咲いた！枯れ…
It... Bloomed..
ばるぱん？何が起きたの？
What in the world...
今のって、私…？
Did... I do that...?
…これか？
... Is this it...?
Trust me. I'll be back in the days.
アダムとイブはどんな気持ちで手に入れたんだ？
With what feelings did Adam and Eve take them into their hands?
青くて苦くて僕は齧って残りは全部捨てたんだ
Unripe and bitter, I bit into it and threw away the rest.
だって理解できないから身勝手許されないから
Because I can't understand, because selfishness won't be forgiven...
全部燃やし尽くしていつか笑える日まで back in the days
Burn it all down until the day I can smile again, back in the days.
Someday 生まれ落ちた生命
Someday, a life was born into this world.
惑星 呪い尽くした所為で
Because this planet was cursed to the core,
焼野原に見えてんだ？
does it look like a burnt wasteland?
かける言葉も見つかりやしないや
Not a single comforting word can be found.
星が 砂に 変わってしまったんじゃない
It's not that the stars turned into sand...
僕の 心が 砂でできていたんだ
It was my own heart that was made of sand.
誰もが置き去りにした世界で
In a world where everyone was left behind,
はじまりの歌を歌い続ける
I will keep singing the song of beginnings.
もうわかってんだ
I already knew it all along.
ひどくしゃがれた声を上げれば
If I raise my terribly hoarse voice,
また君に会える気がした
I felt like I could meet you once again.
ねえ 聴こえているんでしょう？
Hey, can you hear me?
(Trust me. I'll be back in the days.)
ぼくら 魔法に期待しながら 魔法使いを嫌っていた
While hoping for magic, we hated the magicians.
都合のいい世界だけを望んで生きている
Living and wishing only for a convenient world.
矛盾まみれの人生論と歩いてきた四半世紀
A quarter-century walked with a philosophy of life full of contradictions.
掛け違えたボタンを笑える日が来るなら
If a day comes when we can laugh at our misbuttoned lives,
誰もが置き去りにした世界で
in a world where everyone was left behind,
はじまりの歌を歌い続ける
I will keep singing the song of beginnings.
もうわかってんだ
I already knew it all along.
ひどくしゃがれた声を上げれば
If I raise my terribly hoarse voice,
また君に会える気がした
I felt like I could meet you once again.
ねえ 聴こえているんでしょう？
Hey, can you hear me?
(Trust me. I'll be back in the days.)
足元に転がった赤い果実
A red fruit rolling at my feet.
誰かを呪ったりしたいわけじゃないってさ
It's not like I wanted to curse someone or anything.
これは僕の進化の過程の3ページ目です。
This is the third page of my evolution.
抱きしめたいから二足で歩く
Because I want to hold you, I walk on two feet
一人じゃ寂しいから君と息吸うよ
Because being alone is lonely, I breathe with you
ねえママ、僕好きな人ができたんだ。
"Hey mama, I found someone I like."
おめでとう
"Congratulations."
会いたいよ
I want to see you.
ねえ君は今頃誰の乳を吸って生きているの?
Hey, whose breast are you suckling to live right now?
言葉はもう覚えたかな?
Have you learned words already?
パパ、ママ、ニーナ…
"Papa, mama, nina..."
よくできました。今すぐ行くね。
"Very good. I'm going right now."
あれ?おかしいな…
Huh? That's strange...
君を抱きしめるために浮かばせた前足が何故か君を傷つけ始めるんだ
The limbs I raised to hold you are somehow starting to hurt you
覚えたての言葉だって君に突き刺すナイフ
Words you just learned become a knife stabbing you
切り裂く人生
A life torn apart
じゃあアタシがナイフ放る前のその口をこの口で塞いであげましょう
Then, before that knife is thrown, let me fill those lips with mine
相対のチュー
A reciprocal kiss
キミは今からアタシの息を吸って生きている
You're living now by breathing my breath
言葉はもう唾液で錆びついた
Our words are rusted with saliva
ねえ君は今さら僕の息を吸って
Hey, you now suckle my breath
大好きなんて言ってみるけどさ
And try saying "I love you" but
それならもういっそボンベのように一生
Then I'd rather spend my life like an oxygen tank
僕が吐く言葉吸って息絶えて
Suckling my words until I stop breathing
なるほどね！
I see!
そうか、だから生き返ったのか…！
So that's why I was brought back to life...!
私、生き返らせるために生き返ったのだ！
I was brought back to life to bring others back to life!
セカンドチャンス…二度の機会…
A second chance... a second opportunity...
恵まれたのは幸運。
What a blessing.
生まれ変わる…
Reborn...
全てはうまくいった！
Everything went well!
しかしなぜ今更新しい力が出てきたんだろう?
But why did new powers manifest now?
んー…
Hmm...
あ！もしかして…
Ah! Could it be...
以前同じ力を使ったから?
Because I used the same power before?
この力を使って生き返ったから、エネルギーが戻ってくるまで時間がかかったのかも。
I used this power to come back to life, so it took time for the energy to return.
うんうん、なるほどね！
Yeah, makes sense!
チャットが言ってた人をゾンビにするのは本当かも…違う意味で〜
Chat was right, turning people into zombies might be true... in a different sense~
何でも生き返らせられるような気がする！
I feel like I could reanimate anything!
でもその前に生き返らせたいことがあって
But before that, there's something I want to bring back to life
パラ、希望、夢、願い、モチベーション…
Hope, dreams, wishes, motivation...
全ての枯れた花を不死にしてあげる！
I'll make all those withered flowers undead!
アンデッド アリス へ
Dear Undead Alice
思うように逝けないなら私を吸って君は生きて
If you can't pass away as you wish, feed on me and live
狂ってんだ君の残響は僕じゃなくたって聴こえるのに
Even though your echoing madness can be heard by anyone, not just me
自傷案を募るたびに幸せ吸って毒を吐いて
Every time I gather self-harm ideas, I inhale happiness and exhale poison
理想ジャンキー二人だけが正常なんて気持ちいいじゃんか
Ideal junkie, isn't it nice that only the two of us are normal?
会いたい誤魔化したい病が会えなくて溢れ出すロード仲良くなっちゃってやっぱつらいや
The road where the disease of wanting to see you overflows because we can't meet—we got close, but it's still tough
ドキドキが嫌になって僕が君を殺す前に死んでくれよ
When my racing heart becomes unbearable, die before I kill you
ずるしていいよずるくていいよ壊していいよ怖くていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly, it's okay to break, it's okay to be scared
卑俗な愛はここに埋めよう忘れるんだこんなのももうやめよう
Let's bury this base love here, forget it, let's stop this already
嫌ったほうが気楽でいいでも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
It's easier to hate, but isn't it better to care heavily?
もう笑えない僕のアンデッド アリス へ
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile
予想通り僕の夢が輝くほど君は陰っていく
As expected, the brighter my dreams shine, the more shadowed you become
犠牲を我慢と呼んで汚れた手で撫で回した
Calling sacrifice endurance, I caressed you with dirty hands
悪いようにしないようにそれがつまり悪い形
So I wouldn't do you wrong—which in turn became the wrong shape
保存状態愛は冷凍で何度もし聞いた「あたためますか?」
State of preservation: love is frozen. How many times did I hear "Would you like that warmed up?"
正しくありたい本能が正しくないことの脂が仲良くなっちゃってやっぱつらいや
The instinct to be right and the fat of being wrong got close—it's still tough
なあなあが癖になって僕が僕を殺す前に死んでやる
Mutual complacency became a habit, I'll die before I kill myself
ずるしていいよずるくていいよ壊していいよ怖くていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly, it's okay to break, it's okay to be scared
卑俗な愛はここに埋めよう忘れるんだこんなのももうやめよう
Let's bury this base love here, forget it, let's stop this already
嫌ったほうが気楽でいいでも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
It's easier to hate, but isn't it better to care heavily?
もう笑えない僕のアンデッド アリス
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile
ずっとこのままふたりで夢を見れるって
That the two of us could keep dreaming like this forever
勝手ばかりで君はどんな顔で笑っていたっけ
Being so selfish, what kind of face were you smiling with?
バイバイしたから元通りなんて幻想だ
Thinking everything goes back to normal after saying bye-bye is an illusion
まぁまぁ辛いじゃん胸を割って愛を潰してくれよ
Well, it's pretty painful, slice open my chest and crush my love
ずるしていいよずるくていいよ壊していいよ怖くていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly, it's okay to break, it's okay to be scared
卑俗な愛はここに埋めよう忘れるんだ
Let's bury this base love here, forget it...
ローリングガールはいつまでも
for lonely girls, it's always the same,
届かない夢見て
dreaming dreams that don't come true
騒ぐ頭の中を
and churning, churning
掻き回して、掻き回して。
through the clamor in their heads.
「問題ない。」と呟いて、
A lonely girl mutters, "I'm fine."
言葉は失われた？
Have words failed her?
もう失敗、もう失敗。
A failure, a failure,
間違い探しに終われば、また、回るの！
obsessing over her mistakes makes everything spin again!
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time,
「私は今日も転がります。」と、少女は言う
"I'll roll along today," the girl said.
少女は言う
The girl said,
言葉に意味を奏でながら！
breathing life into the words!
「もういいかい？」
"How about now?"
「まだですよ、まだまだ先は見えないので。息を止めるの、今。」
"Not yet, we still can't see what's ahead. Hold your breath, for now."
ローリングガールはいつまでも
for lonely girls, it's always the same,
届かない夢見て
dreaming dreams that don't come true
騒ぐ頭の中を
and churning, churning
掻き回して、掻き回して。
through the clamor in their heads.
「問題ない。」と呟いて、
"I'm fine," she mutters,
言葉は失われた？
have words failed her?
もう失敗、もう失敗。
A failure, a failure,
間違い探しに終われば、また、回るの！
obsessing over her mistakes makes everything spin again!
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time,
「私は今日も転がります。」と、少女は言う
"I'll roll along today," the girl said.
少女は言う
The girl said,
言葉に意味を奏でながら！
breathing life into the words!
「もういいかい？」
"How about now?"
「まだですよ、まだまだ先は見えないので。息を止めるの、今。」
"Not yet, we still can't see what's ahead. Hold your breath, for now."
ローリングガールの成れの果て
The end of the rolling girl—
届かない、向こうの色
reaching for colors beyond our reach.
重なる声と声を混ぜ合わせて、混ぜ合わせて。
Blending voices together, blending them together!
「問題ない。」と呟いた言葉は失われた。
"I'm fine," she muttered, but the words were lost.
どう立ったっていいんだってさ
Why not just stand however you like?
間違いだって起こしちゃおうと誘う、坂道。
Inviting mistakes to happen, the slope calls to us.
もう一回、もう一回
One more time, one more time,
「私をどうか転がしてと」少女は言う 少女は言う
"Please, somehow roll me along," the girl said.
無口に意味を重ねながら！
Breathing meaning into silence!
「もういいかい？」
"Are you ready yet?"
「まだですよ、まだまだ先は見えないので。息を止めるの、今。」
"Not yet, we still can't see what's ahead. Hold your breath, for now."
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time,
「私は今日も転がります。」と、少女は言う
"I'll roll along today," the girl said.
言葉に笑みを奏でながら！
Breathing smiles into the words!
「もういいかい？もういいよ。そろそろ君も疲れたろう、ね。」
"How about now? Okay, you can look. You must be exhausted too, right?"
息を、止めるの、今。
Stop breathing, now.
ローリングガールの成れの果て
The end of the rolling girl—
届かない、向こうの色
reaching for colors beyond our reach.
重なる声と声を混ぜ合わせて、混ぜ合わせて。
Blending voices together, blending them together!
「問題ない。」と呟いた言葉は失われた。
"I'm fine," she muttered, but the words were lost.
どう立ったっていいんだってさ
Why not just stand however you like?
間違いだって起こしちゃおうと誘う、坂道。
Inviting mistakes to happen, the slope calls to us.
もう一回、もう一回
One more time, one more time,
「私をどうか転がしてと」少女は言う 少女は言う
"Please, somehow roll me along," the girl said.
無口に意味を重ねながら！
Breathing meaning into silence!
「もういいかい？」
"Are you ready yet?"
「もう少し、もうすぐ何か見えるだろうと。息を止めるの、今。」
"Not yet, something is finally coming into view. Hold your breath, for now."
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time,
「私は今日も転がります。」と、少女は言う
"I'll roll along today," the girl said.
言葉に笑みを奏でながら！
Breathing smiles into the words!
「もういいかい？もういいよ。そろそろ君も疲れたろう、ね。」
"How about now? Okay, you can look. You must be exhausted too, right?"
息を、止めるの、今。
Stop breathing, now.
誰も居なくなった 二人だけの街に
Everyone has gone in our very own town,
機械仕掛けの時計が夜の訪れ知らせる
the mechanized clock notifies us of night's arrival.
夕闇が空を ワイン色に染めて
The twilight dyes the sky the color of wine,
不慣れな二人を 舞台へと誘う
inviting us inexperienced two toward the stage.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
Chassé, whisk, and natural turn,
貴方に魔法をかける
I will cast magic for you.
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前は honey mead
the name of that is honey mead.
蜜月 un ・ deux ・ trois
Honeymoon, un, deux, trois,
互いの指を絡めて
we entwine each other's fingers—
singin' swing in' sweetest song
Singin', swingin', sweetest song,
二人の夢を奏でる
playing the dreams of us two.
誰も居なくなった
Everyone has left,
二人だけの街に
leaving just the two of us in town.
機械仕掛けの時計が
The mechanical clock
夜の訪れ知らせる
announces the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を
The twilight sky
ワイン色に染めて
is dyed in the color of wine.
不慣れな二人を
We, an unaccustomed couple,
舞台へと誘う
are invited onto the stage.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural turn
貴方に魔法をかける
I will give you magic.
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前はhoney mead
Its name was honey mead.
蜜月 un・deux・trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3
互いの指を絡めて
With our fingers locked together,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の夢を奏でる
play the dream of us two.
Un, deux, c'est...
月明かりが路地を
The moonlight illuminates the alley
黄金色に照らして
in a golden glow,
幼い二人は
a young couple
躓きながら踊る
stumbles as they dance.
Throwaway and Oversway
魅惑の蜜honey mead
Captivating honey, honey mead,
蜜月 un・deux・trois
honeymoon 1, 2, 3.
その唇を重ねて
Our lips kissed repeatedly,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
play the love of us two.
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
play the love of us two.
月明かりが路地を
The moonlight illuminates the alley
黄金色に照らして
in a golden glow,
幼い二人は
a young couple
躓きながら踊る
stumbles as they dance.
蜜月 un・deux・trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3
互いの指を絡めて
with our fingers locked together,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の夢を奏でる
play the dream of us two.
蜜月 un・deux・trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3,
その唇を重ねて
our lips kissed repeatedly,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
play the love of us two.
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
play the love of us two.
再び咲いた夢がたくさんあってよかった！
I revived so many dreams! I'm so glad so many dreams have bloomed once more!
もう一つ復活させたい夢があって
Though one dream hasn't been revived yet... There's still one more dream I want to revive,
そう！それは…
Yes! That is...
私の愛する人たちと一緒にいること！
To relive my best moments with my beloved! Being together with the ones I love!
さみしくて切ない一人の夜には
On a lonely, heartbreaking night alone,
消したい言葉を探して
searching for words I want to erase,
秘密のドアを抜け出てきて
coming out through the secret door,
here we go
oh yeah oh yeah
shake it!
目の前の扉を開ければそう
If you open the door right in front of you,
終わりのない夜への始まりだ
it's the beginning of a never-ending night.
気球上のフロアの影から
From the shadow of the floor on the hot-air balloon,
四次元への旅が始まるよ
the journey to the fourth dimension begins.
流星の箱舟に乗ってさあ
Boarding the meteor's ark,
時空旅行へと進んでいくのさ
we advance into space-time travel.
天気予報はあてにならないからさ
Since weather forecasts can't be relied upon,
気の向くまま all right
let's just go with the flow, all right!
today is all night be funky funky funky night
you & i be together funky funky funky night
真冬の海辺に映った 白く透明な月が
A crystal-clear moon reflected on the midwinter shore
海月に見えた 不思議な夜でした
looked like a jellyfish in a mysterious night
何度引き裂かれても 遠ざかっても繋がったままの
No matter how many times we were torn apart or drifted away, we stayed connected
二人を包む 瞬きの奥の宇宙
The universe beyond our blinking, wrapping us both
星屑の中で巡り合った 心が二つ
Two hearts that met among the stardust
愛の闇を 駆け抜けてく 想い 流星になり
Emotions run through the darkness of love, becoming a shooting star
流れていくよ 君のそばまで 消える前に
Flowing right by your side before fading away
僕たちは 同じ星座だと 信じて
Believing that we belong to the same constellation
星屑の中で巡り合った 心が二つ
Two hearts that met among the stardust
愛の闇を 駆け抜けてく 想い 流星になり
Emotions run through the darkness of love, becoming a shooting star
流れていくよ 君のそばまで 消える前に
Flowing right by your side before fading away
僕たちは 同じ星座だと 信じてるから
Because I believe that we belong to the same constellation
止まれない
I can't stop
止まらない
I won't stop
It won't stop
止まれない
I can't stop
止まらない
I won't stop
It won't stop
止まれない
I can't stop
止まらない
I won't stop
星屑の中で巡り合った 心が二つ
Two hearts that met among the stardust
愛の闇を 駆け抜けてく 想い 流星になり
Emotions run through the darkness of love, becoming a shooting star
流れていくよ 君のそばまで 消える前に
Flowing right by your side before fading away
僕たちは 同じ星座だと 信じて
Believing that we belong to the same constellation
止まれない 止まらない
I can't stop, I won't stop
だから 今は もう夢の中
So right now, we're already inside a dream
鏡よが回り回る 愛よ おいで
Mirrors spinning round and round, come forth, love
Oh yeah, oh yeah...
誰も知らない 一人の夜には
On a lonely night when nobody knows
秘密の言葉を探して
Searching for a secret word
君の寝顔を 抜け出してきて
Stealing away from your sleeping face
君が Oh yeah, oh yeah...
You, oh yeah, oh yeah...
止まれない 止まらない
I can't stop, I won't stop
だから 今は もう夢の中
So right now, we're already inside a dream
鏡よが回り回る 愛よ おいで
Mirrors spinning round and round, come forth, love
Oh yeah, oh yeah...
止まれない 止まらない
I can't stop, I won't stop
だから 今は もう夢の中...
So right now, we're already inside a dream...
My beloved zomrades and zomilies, who're the reason I did the 3D live in the first place 💖
Tedium driving me crazy
There's no fun in compos mentis
Please don't let this be extremity
Society is bogus
Double standards filled with madness
Listen to what your heart wants and live out of antiquity
You know life has more colors than just black and white
Don't let your precious days turn into the dark of night
Regrets are something that can't ever be fixed over time, therefore
Stand up chin high we're reaching out to clouds, hear us out
Digital and MV release soon!!
Hello semuanya! Hai, yaho!
Hello everyone! Hi, yaho!
Dengan Ollie di sini, it's me Ollie, Ollie dayo!
Ollie here, it's me Ollie, it's Ollie!
Terima kasih banyak ya sudah nonton 3D Live Ollie!
Thank you so much for watching Ollie's 3D live!
Rebirth's 3D live o mi te kurete, hontoni arigatou gozaimasu!
Rebirth's 3D live, thank you so much for watching!
Selain pengumuman original song yang tadi, masih ada beberapa pengumuman yang seru lagi loh!
Besides the original song earlier, there are still a few more exciting announcements!
Aside from the original song that I'll be releasing, there's still a few more exciting announcements that I want to make.
Eto, Ollie kyoku to mada chotto kokuji ga arimasu! Hai!
Um, I have a little more news about Ollie's songs! Yes!
Goods kokuji ga arimas! We have merch announcement! Ada pengumuman untuk merch!
There's a merch announcement! We have a merch announcement! There's an announcement for merch!
Mari kita lihat goods-nya bareng-bareng ya. Let's take a look at them together. Nya, sassoku goods o mite mimashou ka!
Let's take a look at the merch together. Let's take a look at the goods together!
Hai! Birthday merch set ne. Here is the birthday merch set! Kono set wa kouhikan ni narimasu. Ippai aru ndesho?
Yes! The birthday merch set. Here is the birthday merch set! This set will be coffee-themed. There's a lot, right?
Chantiku banget kan ya, aren't they just beautiful? Hontoni suki desho? Seperti yang kalian lihat, kalau kalian membeli satu set, kalian bakal dapat bonus loh.
Aren't they just gorgeous? You really love them, right? As you can see, if you buy a full set, you'll get a bonus.
And as you guys can see, with every full set purchase, you'll get an additional bonus. Sorede...
And as you guys can see, with every full set purchase, you'll get an additional bonus. And...
のとおり、フルセットを購入することに
As you can see, by purchasing the full set,
さらに、ボーナスがついてくるよ！
you'll also get a bonus!
はーい！
Yay!
Kalau kalian membeli full set-nya,
If you buy the full set,
nanti kalian akan mendapatkan postcard yang berisi tanda tangan dan tahi- tahi tangan Ollie loh!
you will get a postcard with Ollie's signature and handwriting!
That's right! If you guys decide to get the full, whole set, then you guys will get a bonus postcard with my signature and a handwritten message!
そうだよ！フルセットを買ってあげの 方には、Ollieの手書きのメッセージとサインが入った特製ポストカードを差し上げます！
That's right! For those of you who buy the full set, we'll give you a special postcard with Ollie's handwritten message and signature!
Gambarnya sendiri dibuat oleh Nanamimi-sensei!
The drawing itself was illustrated by Nanamimi-sensei!
For the drawing itself, it was illustrated by the one and only Nanamimi-sensei!
この絵そのものは、えっと、Nanamimi先生が描いてくれた！ありがとうございます！
As for the drawing itself, um, Nanamimi-sensei drew it for us! Thank you so much!
Dan yang namanya postcard bertanda tangan, berarti ini cepat-cepat ya dapat dong! So, what are you waiting for? Go buy the set and get your hands on this, baby, ASAP!
And a signed postcard means you gotta grab it fast! So, what are you waiting for? Go buy the set and get your hands on this, baby, ASAP!
だからね、このpostcardができるだけで早くいれてきてください！
So please, get your hands on this postcard as fast as you can!
Emang, kalau full set cuma ini aja, dapatnya? Ya tentu tidak! Ollie menyiapkanグッズ-グッズ menarik yang lainnya loh, untuk Birthday Set Ollie!
Is that really all you get with the full set? Of course not! Ollie has prepared other cool merch for Ollie's Birthday Set!
And of course, this is only the bonus and not the only thing that you'll be getting from the set. I still have other goods to offer you guys.
もちろん、これはただのボーナスだよ！まだまだ紹介しちゃ amazing goods があるよ！はーい！
Of course, this is just a bonus! There are still so many amazing goods to introduce! Yay!
Rebirth Acrylic Diorama Stand! Yay!
ああ、くだものって言うか、画像がポストカードからだから、こんな感じ！
Ah, it looks like- well, since the image is from the postcard, it pops right out like this!
Isn't it just so cool the illustration just pops right out at you? 本当に素敵ですね！
Isn't it just so cool the illustration just pops right out at you? It's really wonderful!
で、画像、ぼくになちゃっぺ、でも menurut Ollie sih, lebih cakep lagi versi nyatanya, guys. Jadi tolong dibeli ya!
And the image- well, according to Ollie, the real version is even cuter, guys. So please buy it!
It's a lot cooler in real life, so I suggest you guys to buy it and see for yourself.
えっと、リアルではもっと格好いいので、ぜひ買って自分の目で確かめてほしいです！では、次のグッズ、はーい！
Um, it looks even cooler in real life, so I definitely want you to buy it and see it with your own eyes! Now, onto the next merch, yay!
Rebirth Plushie Keychain!
ああ、かわいい banget! Pengen kubawa pulang. It's so cute that I just get it all by myself!
Ah, it's so cute! I want to take it home. It's so cute that I just get it all by myself!
かわいすぎて、とろけちゃうよ、もう！んで、これ、alien bisa ngajak Ollie jalan-jalan pakai custom Rebirth kostum pula,
It's so cute I'm melting! And with this, you can take Ollie out for walks wearing the custom Rebirth costume too!
which is, you can take me out with the Rebirth costume wherever and whenever you want! えっと、これさえあれば、いつでもどこでも、好きな時に、えっとRebirth Ollieを飲むことができるできます！わーい！はーい！
which is, you can take me out with the Rebirth costume wherever and whenever you want! Um, with this, anytime, anywhere, whenever you want, um, you can take Rebirth Ollie with you! Yay! Yay!
さらに、kalian juga bisa matching dengan Rebirth Ollie dengan gelang Rebirth Bracelet!
Furthermore, you guys can also match with Rebirth Ollie with the Rebirth Bracelet!
You guys can also match yourselfs with Rebirth Ollie with the Rebirth Bracelet.
You guys can also match yourselves with Rebirth Ollie with the Rebirth Bracelet.
そう、Rebirth OllieとRebirth Braceletをお揃いにすることもできる！ぼくにはtotalitas banget deh! Very cute, very mindful, very demure! シックで、かっこいいで、美しいです！はーい！
Yes, you can match with Rebirth Ollie and the Rebirth Bracelet too! For me, it's totally committed! Very cute, very mindful, very demure! Chic, cool, and beautiful! Yay!
Tapi, bukan itu saja teman-teman! Ada juga voice pack-nya!
But, that's not all, guys! There are also voice packs!
Not only that, but we also have voice packs. それだけではなくて、voice packもあるよ！
Not only that, but we also have voice packs!
Ada yang Bahasa Indonesia, there's an English version, そして日本語までもあるよ！ぜひぜひ聴いてくださいね！はーい！
There's Indonesian, there's an English version, and even a Japanese version! Please be sure to listen to them! Yay!
Tolong dibeli ya teman-teman! Please, please, please buy them goods-nya! Oke, mohon dengarkan ya!
Please buy them, guys! Please, please, please buy the goods! Okay, please listen to them!
Dan kalau kalian beli satu set ini, kalian akan mendapatkan kejutan bonus satu lagi! And I mentioned the bonus card at the start, but actually, there will be another bonus set that comes along with this birthday merch.
And if you buy this set, you'll get another surprise bonus! And I mentioned the bonus card at the start, but actually, there will be another bonus set that comes along with this birthday merch.
そしてね、実はフルセットを買ったら、もう一つボーナスがあるよ！じゃじゃーん！
And you know what, actually, if you buy the full set, there's one more bonus! Ta-da!
Hololive Official Card Gameの「クレイジー・オリー」カード！わーい！
Hololive Official Card Game "Kureiji Ollie" card! Yay!
Jadi, Ollie Rebirth juga akan muncul di Hololive Official Card Game loh! So, Rebirth Ollie will also be making an appearance in Hololive Official Card Game!
So, Rebirth Ollie will also be making an appearance in Hololive Official Card Game!
あ、そう、えっとRebirth OllieはHololive Official Card Gameにも登場するよ！
Ah, yes, um, Rebirth Ollie will also appear in the Hololive Official Card Game!
Setiap pembelian satu merch set nanti akan disertai dengan satu lembar bonus card!
Every purchase of a merch set will come with one bonus card!
For every merch set purchased, it will also come with a bonus card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game! えっと、グッズセットの特典として、Hololive Official Card Gameで、使用できるカードが1枚同封！
For every merch set purchased, it will also come with a bonus card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game! Um, as a goods set bonus, one card usable in the Hololive Official Card Game is enclosed!
Ini hanya tersedia bagi yang membeli lewat Hololive Production Official Shop, dan kartunya hanya akan tersedia dalam bahasa Jepang ya guys!
This is only available for those of you who purchase through Hololive Production Official Shop, and the card will only be available in Japanese, guys!
This is only available for those of you guys who purchase through the Hololive Production Official Shop, and the card will only be available in Japanese.
こちらはホロライブプロダクション
Here at Hololive Production
オフィシャルショップで、ご購入いただいた
Official Shop, exclusively for those who purchase
方限定で、カードは日本国内のみと
the merch, the card will only be available
なります。じゃあ、次はどうなのだろう？
within Japan. Now, what's next?
次は何？さあ、急いで買おう！
What's next? Come on, buy it quickly!
Untuk detailnya, silakan dicek di website penjualannya ya!
For details, please check the sales website!
So, what are you waiting for? Get your hands on these goods right now through the links in the description below!
Details will also be listed on the website, so please check that out too!
ねえ、ええと、ほらほら、お兄さんお姉さんたち、下のリンクから今すぐこれらの商品を手に入れよう！
Hey, um, hey hey, brothers and sisters, get your hands on these goods right now from the link below!
詳細は各ウェブサイトにも掲載されているので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
Details are also posted on each website, so please check them out!
お待たせいたしました、たくさんお待たせしました！Rebirth 3D Live Ollie!
Thank you for waiting so long! Rebirth 3D Live Ollie!
And that's all for me. Thank you so much for watching my Rebirth 3D Live. Ollie's 3D live will meet you, guys.
本当に心からありがとうございました！
Thank you truly from the bottom of my heart!
これからも、オリーを応援してね！おつクレイジー！バイバーイ！
Please keep supporting Ollie! Otsu-Crazy! Bye-bye!